- Excuse me, Penny, but we're...
- Don't tell her.
(Sheldon:)...playing Klingon Boggle.
[GROANS]
What do you mean, "Ohh?"
Like she didn't know we were nerds?
(Sheldon:)All right, if you must watch,
then mute it with closed captions, please.
(Leonard:)Fine.
(Sheldon:)All right, Boggle warriors.
[SPEAKS IN KLINGON]
(Howard:)Look at those women.
(Leonard:)They're gorgeous.
Oh, worf. Nice.
(Sheldon:)Too bad that's a proper noun.
(Howard:)Oh, look,
there's the future Mrs. Wolowitz.
(Howard:)No wait, that's the future Mrs. Wolowitz.
(Howard:)With her head in the lap of...
(Howard:)What a coincidence.
It's the future Mrs. Wolowitz.
(Leonard:)Yeah, and they can all move in
with you and your mother.
(Leonard:)The current Mrs. Wolowitz.
Is qochbe spelled with
a "qo" or a "ko?"